We also have right clicks on these options on these items and on these objects so for example
I right click on this image and as you see I can cut, I can copy object, I can paste,
I can duplicate, I can delete, I can flip for example as you see you know so what else
I can position, I can align, I can lock, I can set as background you know this is how
it will happen so again if I right click I can this time say detach image from
background yes and what else can I do I can use content credentials right about the image history
and origin so this is also very useful it goes and search about this very image and says that
where this image comes from etc so I press control z and control z again so I go back to
how it was what else do we have on a right click on this text for example nothing new we just
can click on rewrite or copy text styles and that's all you know nothing more nothing newer